shimply.com 2015-06-30

# Privacy Policy

Shimply grants you a non-exclusive right and license to access & use the website for personal, non-commercial purposes, other than to purchase or sell items through the Site's, or to purchase items from third-party merchants accessible via links on the Site. This license does not include and strictly prohibits: any resale of the site or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices other than as expressly authorized herein, any derivative use of the website or its contents; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. The site, including its operation, interface and contents, are covered by Indian copyright laws and international laws and treaties, and may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any unauthorized commercial purpose without the express prior written consent of Shimply. Any unauthorized use shall immediately terminate the licenses and rights granted by Shimply and any Licensors hereunder, and may subject you to civil and/or criminal prosecution. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to any page of the Site so long as the link does not portray Shimply, its subsidiaries, affiliates, Licensors, co-brand partners and other partners or its or their respective services in a false, misleading, derogatory or otherwise offensive or damaging manner. You may not use any Shimply, Licensor, subsidiary, affiliate, co-brand partner, or other partner logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of a link to the website without first obtaining the express written consent of Shimply, the subsidiary, affiliate, co-brand partner or other partner or Licensor (as applicable). 

Shimply doesn't guarantee continuous, uninterrupted or secure access to its services or the website, and the operation of the website may be interfered with by numerous factors outside or within Shimply control. 

## Children's Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to use this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our website only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. 

## Privacy Policy

Shimply, we want you to know exactly how and when we collect and use information that can specifically identify you, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address ("personal information"). 

We do not require that you provide, nor do we collect, any personal information if you are just browsing the Site. We may offer on the Site non-transactional and transaction based services ("Service(s)") in which, subject to applicable terms and availability, you may participate (e.g., submitting product reviews or becoming a member to buy or sell items. In order to provide you with the services you request, Shimply may require that you first provide certain personal information, which we determine is reasonably necessary in order for us to fulfill your request. If you indicate an interest in participating in a service, we will identify what specific personal information you must provide prior to collecting such information. Any personal information which we collect from you will only be used for the purposes identified in this privacy statement, the Shimply terms of use and your applicable member agreement with Shimply, and as may otherwise be indicated at the time the information is collected. To update, modify or delete any personal information you provide to us with respect to a Service you may access your account with Shimply under my account section. 

## Cookie Information:

The Site contains cookie technology, which collects non-personal information about you which is used to customize the website for your future use. 

## Copyrights and Trademarks

All internal/external content, graphics, format, design, logo are trademarks of their respective owners except the Shimply user interface which is owned by Shimply and/or its licensors and/or partners. Company and product/service names displayed on this website may be the trade marks or copy right of their respective owners. Users are not granted any right or licence to use any trademarks contained herein. All Logos, Images, Names used on pricinindia.in are property of their respective owners. Shimply does not have any direct affiliation with these merchants. 

If any graphic, content, coupons codes, deals, product, brand names on Shimply should not be here and you feel its your property and you dont want it to be a part of the free promotion on Shimply, you can request it to be removed from the website by simply sending a request to here 

## User contribution

All reviews, coupons, discounts, images, price offers submitted by online users are property of respective users, under cc by-sa 3.0 In addition, Shimply records IP Address, Name, Submit Date of users submitting information on the wesbite and can be provided on any infringement complain to copyright owners. All respective copright owner can ask to edit/delete their property from Shimply by submitting request here with a notice of 60 days.
